[Music] It looks like he's
[Música]
screwed up in the
tiene toda la pinta de que la caga en el
previous excerpt, guys, let's see,
extracto anterior chavales a ver
and it's that they cut off the recording, it does
y es que nos han cortado la grabación
n't cut the recording, but well, I'll
no corta la grabación pero bueno ya la
cut it with the YouTube editor, it's okay, what's
corto con el editor de youtube no pasa
up, guys? Well, let's
na que pasan chavalería bueno vamos a
relate a very interesting video
relacionar un videito muy interesante
that my team of kids sent me, it's
que me ha mandado mi equipo de
that you sent me the
chavalería es que me habéis mandado los
videos, you
vídeos
sent me a video
me habéis mandado un vídeo
how he explains why he wanted to hit the
como explica el por qué quería golpear
best during the World Balloon Championships and
al mejor durante el mundial de globos y
the best responded to Momo today so I
el mejor le respondió hoy a momo así que
imagine I'll have to watch it, both of them, I do
me imagino que tendré que verlo los dos
n't have them either, both of them or the million
no tengo también los dos o el millón
reacts to the other in the other one, I don't have to
reacciona al otro en el otro no tengo
know, both of them, not
saberlo los dos no
literally in duel, both of them, well, nothing, let's
literalmente de duelo los dos pues nada
see, let's see, first I
vamos a ver vamos a ver primero me
imagine it would be first with a host
imagino que sería primero con
[Applause] We're
[Aplausos]
going to tell it because people
lo vamos a contar porque la gente
like this were the ones who threatened water and
como este fue el que amenazó agua y
Michu
michu
who went tremendously crazy
que se le fue tremendamente la olla
because no matter how much nonsense he
porque por mucho que por mucha jilipoyez
put in, oh Michu, you don't have to
que pusiera uy michu no tienes que
threaten anyone with physical violence,
amenazar con violencia física a nadie
honestly, without service, the mind
sinceramente sin servicio la mente
the momo was the one who threatened a bond
el momo fue el que amenazó a un vínculo
opens the door to [ __ ] we were
es abre la puerta a pollas estábamos
here eating and eating and eating for
aquí comiendo y comiendo y comiendo para
more to go to portaventura and says come on
más para ir a portaventura y dice vamos
friends friends well the mitger no no no no
amigos amigos bien el mitger no no no no
I'll punch him and while asleep
yo le hago un puñetazo y dormido
you're going to hit a person at an event and he
vas a pegar a una persona en un evento y
tells me how am I not going to hit anyone he
me dice cómo no voy a pegar nadie me
says yes but when the event is over alive
dice sí pero cuando acabe el evento viva
and calm does this I mean the two of us
y tranquilo hace esto o sea los dos
were eating
estábamos comiendo
look they laugh aha who was it will get
es que mire se ríen aja quien era se
attached to someone ha ha what are the things
apegará a alguien ja ja qué de las cosas
that have how funny this is what
que tiene que gracioso esto es lo que
happens because even if it's six famous people to
pasa porque sea seis famosos a
anyone okay I think that for those in
cualquiera vale yo creo que para los en
the slums I
los barrios bajos
mean in the slums people who are
o sea en los barrios bajos gente que sea
slums okay they have to stay
barriobajera vale se tienen que quedar
there okay unless they are willing to
ahí vale a no ser que estén dispuestos a
change it's so nobody is offended by the
cambiar es que nadie se ofenda a los
big ones offering that someone is from a
grandes ofrenda de que alguien sea de un
humble bar but you can be from a
bar de humildes pero se puede ser de un
humble neighborhood without being a slum dweller
barrio humilde sin ser un barriobajero
okay but this attitude of a square
vale pero esta actitud de plazoleta
from threatened I hit you I'm the coolest
desde amenazó te pego soy el más guay
because I hit more no kids when you're
porque pegó más no chavales cuando estás
here already in a medium your mind  has to
aquí ya en un medio tu mente tiene que
open up and learn and mature and grow
abrirse y aprender y madurar y crecer
physical threats never to anyone never no one
amenazas físicas nunca a nadie nunca no
is cooler the one who hits the best the
es más guay el que mejor pega el más
coolest the one who humiliates you the most for
guay el que más te humilla por los
arguments the best talker and the most
argumentos que mejor habla y el más
intelligent okay
inteligente vale
look I hit him I hit him after the event the one who
mira le pego le pego después del evento
is made for what has
que el que está hecho para que le ha
hit him the first one has done something to
pegado el primero ha hecho algo a
someone in your family no no no don't
alguien de tu familia no no no no se
confuse this fact sometimes threatening to
confunda a este hecho a veces amenazar a
hit someone or seeing normal and
alguien con pegarle o ver normal y
fix things getting attached is
arreglar las cosas apegarse es de
low-class okay I'm from a
barriobajero vale yo soy de un barrio
humble neighborhood I'm from a humble neighborhood but you
humilde yo soy un barrio humilde pero tú
can be from a humble neighborhood without being
puedes ser de un barrio humilde sin ser
a low-class person I don't think you understand
un barriobajero yo creo no me entendéis
the definition of low-class okay
la definición de barriobajero vale
the hands almost also nothing it is
las manos casi también nada que
simply like that and with this youtube thing
simplemente es así y con esto de youtube
many times six famous people to
por muchas veces seis famosos a gente a
anyone
cualquiera
anyone you give followers and you
a cualquiera le dais seguidores y le
give them power and you make them famous anyone
dais poder y hacéis famosa cualquiera
okay
vale
and the momo comes and says I'll serve him
y llega el momo y dice yo le sirvo
transmitter he gets so I'm going to beat the [ __ ] out of him my
transmisor se pone tan voy a a
friend well you can say
trompadas yo amigo bueno puedes decir
that we Argentines are a gang of
que los argentinos somos una banda de
photos that can't read I can't say
fotos que no sabemos leer no puedo decir
this because it will end up in you  and it starts like this we
esto porque te acaba trompadas y empieza
say moment you
así decimos momento
know that Shakira is at the event with
sabe que está en el evento shakira con
her children
sus niños
[Laughs]
[Risas]
with her children who are like wanting
con sus hijos que estén como queriendo
but not as she wanted to be the best well a
pero no como quería sea el mejor pues un
meme dust that I did not know this
meme polvillo que no me enteré de esto
but well with everything he put a meme that
pero bueno con todo él puso un meme de
the Argentines did not know how to read and I
que los argentinos no sabían leer y
found one day reading a book backwards
halle un día leyendo un libro al revés
that the Argentines of trafficking and past with
que los argentinos de trata y pasado con
which to play awards me and I do not know what and I
los que jugar me awards y no sé qué y
momo a lot and that is why you want to create
momo mucho y por eso quieres crear
someone one day as if this were
alguien un día como si esto fuese
second of the that like speaking badly of
segundo de la eso en plan hablado mal de
my friend I'm going to hit you
mi amigo te voy a pegar una
Perez I do not know if it is too much to ask but
pérez no sé si es mucho pedir pero
we are at an event for a million
estamos en un evento para del millón de
people please do not hit each other he does not
personas por fa no te pegues no
speak and
habla y
then he left like well
después dejó como bueno
what is happening
que qué pasa
and I am we are there you know with the
y yo estoy estamos ahí tú sabes con la
beer I do not know what and I see master I go to the
cervecita no sé qué y veo amo voy al
million sitting on the floor talking very
millón sentados en el suelo hablando muy
close I say in one of these a headbutt
cerca digo en una de estas un cabezazo
from the monkey 100 and they were talking and he says
del mono 100 y estaban hablando y dice
that he approached the million he told him
que él se acercó al millón le dijo
because the million he told him first they have
porque el millón le dijo a el de primera
told me that he is not very happy
me han dicho que no está muy contento
with me there is a  mole around here, it's not known
conmigo hay un topo por aquí no se sabe
who he is, but someone told him
quién es pero alguien le dijo
and so, they sat down to talk
y yo sobre pues se sentaron a hablar las
things out. I never knew who he was and
cosas yo yo nunca supe quién era tal y
apparently he calmed down a lot, but
por lo visto se calmó mucho pero
we did
nosotros
n't. The
no
worst thing is that he's right,
lo peor es que tiene razón los
Argentinians are pathetic worldwide,
argentinos damos pena a nivel mundial la
most of them are like that, they think they're better
gran parte son así de creerse mejores
than everyone else or they solve things by
que el resto o lo solucionan a los
hitting each other. How badly we look in the eyes of the civilized world. He
golpes qué mal quedamos ante el mundo
arrived as if in the morning of the event,
llegó como lado de la mañana del evento
the pineapple stood out, so and so, and look, having dinner
destacó la piña tal y cual y vea cenando
together,
juntos
it's like if something happens to you with
es que si te pasa algo con alguien que
someone, let's see, you tell me that
alguien a ver que tú me digas a mi que
they want to hit someone because just
les quiere pegar a alguien porque es que
because I say a criticism of your country, it does
porque te diga una crítica a tu país es
n't make sense. God, this was the one who
que no tiene sentido dios este fue el
said he wanted to hit a bug. Do
que dijo que le quería pegar a un
you also remember why Hui Cho made
también os acordáis porque hui cho hizo
a dark joke about Maradona?
un chiste negro con maradona
Hey, what happens if you hit someone here
oye qué pasa si le pegas a alguien aquí
in Spain and you're traveling from
en españa y vivir estás de viaje desde
another country and you hit someone while you're
otro país y le pegas a alguien estando
here in Spain,
aquí en españa
what would happen illegally
qué pasaría ilegalmente
if you're traveling here in Spain and you
si estás de viaje aquí en españa y le
hit someone, what will the police do to you? They
pegas a alguien que te hace la policía
were having dinner together next door.
estaban cenando juntos al lado
100 euro fine for home or did he
100 euros de multa para casa o hizo
quickly
rápido
apply it and from Spain but to see the
6 aplicarla y de españa pero a ver
background they don't let him enter
antecedentes no lo dejan entrar más en
Spain anymore what would happen because in the US
españa que lo que pasaría porque en eeuu
apart from kicking him out of the country they no longer enter you know I don't
aparte de echarlo del país ya no entran
think I say it much I have to is that I have
no creo que yo lo digo mucho tengo que
always been very surprised by
es que siempre me han sorprendido mucho
the people from Argentina man the personality
la peña de argentina tío la personalidad
come on sea every time that people have people with
vamos mar cada que tiene la gente de
marked personalities that is not
personas personalidad marcada eso no
being well civilized
estar bien civilizado
that they are a civilized person and if you don't like
de que sea una persona civilizada y si
someone you destroy them with
una persona te cae mal lo destruyes con
arguments like you have done and with the
argumentos como lo has hecho y con los
points if you are stronger than me or they
puntos en si tú eres más fuerte que yo o
know how to fight better than me or you are more
saben pelear mejor que yo o eres más
animal than me then you are more right
animal que yo entonces tienes más razón
than me because they hit more no it doesn't
que yo porque pegan más no
make sense
no tiene sentido
Argentine and the way of expressing yourself and
argentino y la forma de expresarse y de
speaking but then education and
hablar pero luego de educación y de
personal treatment is one of the best they are
trato personal es una de las mejores son
super hospitable in my life it is
súper hospitalarios en mi vida es
surplus says Juan are you wrong or
superavitaria dice juan estás mal o
perfect I go to the pharmacy
perfecto voy a la farmacia
a doctor
un médico
with a barbecue yesterday of a [ __ ] to then
con un asado ayer de putísima para luego
continue attentive that a part the one that
seguir atento que una parte la que
is simply with Maradona Argentina
simplemente es con maradona argentina
death wants to score a point is that that
muerte quiere meter un punto es que ese
scheme will be that  it would be god honestly it
esquema será ese sería dios sinceramente
makes me laugh that day
me hace gracia ese día
because it's like maradona said then
porque es como dijo maradona entonces
about maradona I'm not going to the event he said it's to
de maradona yo no voy al evento a dijo
inform me that I didn't want to go because
es informar yo que no quería ir porque
because he loads it because he doesn't feel like
porque se lo carga porque no le apetece
throwing punches in a
ponerse a pegar puñetazos en plan
rehearsed way apart there is an acceleration
ensayado aparte hay una aceleración una
something that is
cosa que es
already like because he sells you a greeting to ibai
ya como porque te vende un saludo a ibai
who is surely watching live
que seguro que está viendo en directo
clara receive there and will go a greeting
clara reciba ahí y va a ir un saludo
but iba and don't take these things as a
pero iba y no toméis estas cosas al
joke please I tell you
cachondeo por favor te lo digo
don't take these things as a joke and dance
no toméis estas cosas de broma y baile
0 joke 0 thank you from the heart I tell you
0 broma 0 gracias de corazón te lo digo
we have our differences but zero
tenemos nuestras diferencias pero cero
jokes with this type of things right not to
bromas con este tipo de cosas verdad no
invite people like that people who you think
invitase a gente así a gente que creáis
can get aggressive people who
que se puede poner agresiva a gente que
leave if they want to hit another teammate
se va si quiere pegar a otro compañero
for a for a meme or for a joke or
por una por un meme o por una broma o
for a criticism even if it's imaginary
por una crítica aunque sea imaginarios
that suddenly he wants to hit me
que de repente me quiere pegar a mí
because I'm criticizing this you were not going
porque estoy criticando esto no ibais
zero jokes man you
cero bromas tío
have the power and I juan and you have
tenéis el poder y yo juan y tú tenéis
much more influence than me many brands
mucha más influencia que yo mucho marcas
but this is problematic here telling it
pero problemático esto aquí contarlo
between laughs did not give it does not take much time
entre risas no dio no lleva mucho tiempo
if it is  funny hitting each other like it's a
si es gracioso pegarse como si fuera
good thing that we still haven't paid me
algo bueno que sigamos sin pagarme
against years it was with a taxi driver
contra años fue con un taxista
two years ago it's already happened it's already happened
hace dos años ya ha pasado ya ha pasado
and of course it's true I think you're not going to
y claro es verdad yo creo que tú no a
tell Momo not to hit him and you might
decirle a momo no le pegues y lo mismo
hit him
le pegas
I had the idea like I had the idea very
yo tenía la idea como tenía la idea muy
clear
clara
he was going with the Argentine shield here on his
él iba con el escudo argentina aquí en
chest in proposing he got into it with the
el pecho en plantear metió con los
Argentines I'm going to kill you not to kill but I'm
argentinos te voy a matar no matar pero
going to give you two points inside I
te voy a dar dos puntos dentro de
agree at some point what he said that he
acuerdo en algún momento lo que dijo que
was eating that he was going to get close to a
estaba comiendo que se iba a acercar al
million and he was going to do it
millón y lo iba a hacer
but
pero
as if it were as if they were in
como si fuera como si estuvieran en el
high school since he comes the pimp from the
instituto desde viene el chulo de la
high school mailbox
buzón del instituto
how is a 30 year old guy going to have sex he won't
como va a un tío de 30 años no se
stay he will have these people but there
queda tendrá esta gente pero ahí la
most are 30 you
mayoría tienen 30 no
're not learning from these
estás aprendiendo de estos chavales
Chinese kids how are you going to have sex you're going to come I'm
chinos cómo vas a vas a venir
going to those daughters
le voy a esas hijas
so you can see what life is like since they are
para que ver lo que es la vida ya que
arriving together it's not that you say bah
van llegando juntos no es que digas bah
no we don't know that we are not in
no no sabemos que no estamos en el
school I mean in school I
colegio quiero decir en el colegio yo me
hope that everyone hits each other
espero que todos se peguen de hostias
balls for the exit to you  that I [ __ ]
pelotas para la salida a tú que me cago
on your dead very bad and shawa is the
en tus muertos muy mal y al shawa es el
school but here we have the
colegio pero aquí que tenemos ya los
black balls of the world to hit and also
huevos negro del mundo a pegar y además
an event with piqu shakira and their children
un evento con piqué shakira y sus hijos
on the left and doubting the one in
a la izquierda y dudando la uno en la
physical strength image added and thank you very much
física imagen agregó y muchas gracias
finally what image
por fin de que imagen
also it is incredible the feeling they
además es increíble el sentimiento que
have of protecting theirs that it is not that
tienen de proteger lo suyo que no es que
you say it is an event did not hit it
te digas es un evento no le pegó
then when it ends it is
entonces cuando acabe
not funny if you really go juan it is
no tiene gracia si vais de verdad juan
not funny right we these
no tiene gracia verdad nosotros estos
topics to the place of truth people like that
temas al sitio de verdad gente así
tolerance 0 0 toxicity out bad
tolerancia 0 0 toxicidad fuera mala
vibes out exactly and you are here
vibra fuera exactamente y estáis aquí
laughing and dancing
riendo y baile
but threw tolerance towards an aggression
pero tiró tolerancia hacia una agresión
people like that I was like a lowlife 0
gente así que estuve como barriobajero 0
really but things are fixed
de verdad pero las cosas se arreglan
talking debating
hablando debatiendo
arguing whatever okay but this
argumentando lo que sea vale pero esto
stuck to jan funny what was he going to
se le pegó a jan gracioso que le iba a
hit him no please and 20 shots that the
pegar no por favor y 20 tiros que los
replicas have done in school man
réplicas han hecho en el colegio tío
when are we going to end these things
cuando vamos a acabar con estas cosas
we are in the year 2021 entering 2020
estamos en el año 2021 entrando a 2020
god many of us know what it is like in
dios muchos sabemos lo que es que en el
school in high school a stronger one comes to you  I'll
colegio en el instituto te venga uno más
hit you
fuerte te pego una
and you'll be left with the host now,
y te quedes con la de ahora
I'm sure many people in the chal have lived,
seguros mucha gente en el chal ha vivido
don't stay with the host given because you're
no te quedes con la dado porque
not going to know, they fight the same way he doesn't
no vas a saber pelean igual que él no
look, come on, his influencers have to
mira venga sus influencers tiene que
go please
vaya por favor
the thing my dog gave I follow mono for a
la cosa mi perro dio sigo a mono hace
long time but in this one I don't agree
tiempo pero en esta no estoy de acuerdo
with him and even more so when it can be
con él y más aún cuando se puede
solved by talking but in these that he has already
solucionar hablando pero en estas que ya
seen on several occasions it is that
le ha visto en varias ocasiones es que a
wind michu who I fall like a
wind michu que a mí se me cae como una
paw on the turnip
pata en el nabo
on the internet I
en internet
wanted to hit him because it's a joke
le quería pegar porque es un chiste
maradona what's your turn maradona
maradona que te toca a ti maradona
already gave us we are in 2000 entering
ya nos dio estamos en el 2000 entrando
2022 please this cannot be
en el 2022 por favor esto no se pueden
seen two influencers as powerful
ver dos influencer así de potentes
having a laugh with the sotillo it
echando unas risas con el sotillo de
is really not funny really and vice
verdad no es gracioso de verdad y vice
from the heart is not funny
de corazón no es gracioso
so this inflates my balls I
así es que esto me infla las pelotas yo
tell you the truth is
te lo digo de verdad
that it also inflates my balls a lot he
es que también infla muchísimo las
told me what happened
me contó lo que pasó
great point of dancing bank the model of
gran punto de bailó banco el modelo de
life for his own that is that is real
la vida por los suyos eso es eso es real
and I want that  if something is known or in other words,
y quiero que se sepa algo o sea
to receive that I have messed with your
recibirse a mí que se ha metido con tu
mother or has threatened your mother or has
madre o ha amenazado a tu madre o le ha
attacked your father then of
agredido a tu padre entonces por
course he kicks her in the head for a
supuesto la arranca en la cabeza desde
while but man are we talking
hace falta pero hombre estamos hablando
about an attack on someone because he makes
de una agresión a alguien porque te haga
a joke about the Argentinians some to me
un chiste de los argentinos alguna a mí
is that please
es que por favor
man then it happens you have to be
hombre entonces ya pasa hay que tener
afraid you cannot be designated
miedo no se te puede designar
the opposite I
la contraria
cannot tell you hey well the tracksuit
no puedo decirte oye pues el chándal me
seems ugly to me I am already afraid that if I
parece feo ya tengo miedo a que si
managed to coincide with you at an event
conseguido coincido contigo en un evento
that I could stick an option we already
que pueda pegar una opción ya esto lo
saw this with mister ego do you remember
vimos con el míster ego os acordáis
mister ego that I criticized him that he does not
míster ego que lo critique que no le
disrespect him at all and the guy says he
falta de respeto ninguno y dice el tío
wanted to hit me when I do Sevilla
de me quería pega cuando haga sevilla
man please I
hombre por favor
am going to give my version of what happened and it is going to
voy a dar mi versión de lo que pasó y va
go with everything and a large part of what is going to
a ir con todo y gran parte de lo que va
happen the of what happened today of things
a pasar el de lo que pasó hoy de cosas
that well I did not know the question whoa if they
que bueno yo no supe la cuestión whoa si
invite me to the event of the world cup
me invitan al evento de del mundial de
Euros I did not even know who it is if they are going to
euros yo no sabía ni quién es si van a
go what do I know and someone said to him look you
ir qué sé yo y alguien le dijo mira le
have to tell momo that she will be
tenéis que decir a momo que va a estar
in the million  I don't know if he told me bar I see
en el millón no sé si me lo dijo bar veo
who told me then I tell him
quién me lo dijo entonces yo le digo
enjoy what this guy did no
goza de lo que hizo este este tipo no
then he tells me something I remember it was it was
entonces me dice algo me acuerdo fue fue
something like that something I remember a lot no but I
algo así algo me acuerdo mucho no pero
know that he got into nothing question that
sé que se metió con nada cuestión que
but what are we going to do we were juan
pero qué vamos a hacer estábamos juan
revs I was going and well we are eating this
revés iba y bueno estamos comiendo esto
I tell him wait for the event to end
yo le digo espera que termine el evento
and I'm going to cure him or will he allude to cure I didn't
y lo voy a curar o se aludirá curar no
say it doesn't seem to me that it is his
dije no me parece que sea su
responsibility the example
responsabilidad al ejemplo
applied sorry
perdón aplicado
forgive and charge
perdonad y cargo
or I mean of course we are not here at the
o sea por supuesto no estamos aquí en el
check I am seriously freaking out I am
cheque yo flipo en serio yo flipo de
really freaking out of course we are not
verdad por supuesto no somos los padres
anyone's parents of course we are not we are not
de nadie por supuesto no estamos no
anyone's parents but man if
somos los padres de nadie pero hombre si
we are in front of hundreds of thousands of
estamos ante cientos de miles de
people always daily here we are going to
personas siempre a diario aquí vamos a
see normal that type of attitudes
ver normales ese tipo de actitudes
I am not going to give you an example of anything if my
yo no te voy a dar ejemplo de nada si mi
channel
canal
that
eso
then when we cut it
entonces cuando lo cortamos
if the people that we follow in
si la gente que nosotros seguimos en
this is what society sees it
esto es lo que ve la sociedad
tells that that was going to hit him but
se cuenta eso que le iba a pegar pero
without the best he
sin el mejor se
put on an attitude that when you
ponía en una actitud que cuando tú
have when you have a maximum
tienes cuando tú tienes una máxima
audience you have more responsibility than
audiencia tienes más responsabilidad que
when you have less that is how it is not that you
cuando tienes menos eso es así no es que
have to set an example in terms of
tengas que tampoco dar ejemplo en plan
educating parents  of the kids it's
educar en los padres de los chavales
clear that no but neither laugh take it
está claro que no pero tampoco reírte
analyze these things you don't know it's not
tomarte analiza estas cosas no saben no
for comparing the best that I tell you
es por comparar a lo mejor que te digo
an abuse imagined abuse no
yo un maltrato imaginaron un maltrato no
abuse no that imagine that
un maltrato no que imaginaros que
someone here comes in by phone some
alguien aquí entra por teléfono algunos
of my followers mentioned the one that
de mis seguidores mencionado al que yo
hit my girlfriend yes he hit my girlfriend
le pegó a mi novia si le pegó a mi novia
because she doesn't want to see because he told me how
porque no quiere ver porque me dijo que
great
gran
sevilla fc erviti was [ __ ] and I
sevilla fc erviti era una y le
asked my girlfriend for a night and how beautiful you
pedí una noche a mi novia y qué bella
are god
eres dios
please
por favor
god
dios
please no it's not funny hitting
por favor no no tiene gracia pegarle a
anyone god
nadie dios
that's no use to me says to me here he comes into
que no me sirve dice a mí acá entra en
your house that he hit your dog that he
tu casa que le ha pegado a tu perro que
hit your mother a
le ha pegado a tu madre un tirón de
purse or that he insulted your grandmother
bolso o que ha insultado a tu abuela
ok he scammed grandma well still maybe it
ok ha estafado abuela pues todavía de
's normal
igual es normal
that the police are not down and do
que tampoco está baja la policía y hace
what they let you do but this since
lo que te deja hacer pero esto ya que te
someone tells you a joke or a criticism
diga alguien un chiste o una crítica
when you are an internet personality I don't
cuando eres un personaje de internet no
know really I like where I was going but
sé de verdad me gusta dónde iba pero
then the one who put a crying baby
entonces ahí el que puso un bebé llorón
is you look see this banned for being an
es tú que mira ven esto baneado por
idiot then he tells me anyway come on you're not
entonces me dice igual vamos no
going to  hit at an event that they are going to
le vas a pegar en un evento que van a
do are you going to apologize to Carmen
hacer le vas a pedir disculpas a carmen
already pique I no no if it's going to happen everything is going to
ya pique yo no no si va a pasar todo va
happen after the event nothing thought
a pasar después el evento nada pensaron
that it was going to stay there juanmi I know but
que eso iba a quedar ahí juanmi sé pero
what are we going to do what I'm going to do
qué vamos a hacer yo lo que voy a hacer
and there I told them what had happened in
y ahí les conté que lo había pasado en
them he got into all the Argentinians
ellos se metió con todos los argentinos
he called everyone ignorant and then it
trató a todos de ignorantes y después
was a pretty xenophobic joke not to
fue un chiste bastante xenófobo ni
mention what had happened with
hablar de lo que había pasado con lo de
coco in the corridors of death and your
coco en los corredores ya de muerte y tu
way of making the Argentinian look good is to
manera de dejar bien al argentino es
hit him a couple of times father well
pegarle un par de hostias padre bueno
nothing question that
nada cuestión que
evidently someone wanted to avoid
evidentemente alguien quería evitar que
all this from happening that I you know that
suceda todo esto que yo ustedes saben
is more I never said it publicly
que es más nunca lo dije públicamente
all this was made public and vice and Juan
todo esto lo hizo público y vice y juan
then they make it public Juan and all
entonces lo hacen público juan y todo
this issue but I never said what had
este tema pero yo nunca dije lo que
happened nor is he going to say what happened
había pasado ni va a decir lo que pasó
what was going to happen this was remained in
lo que iba a pasar esta era quedaba en
the inner circle in the middle of the event
el círculo íntimo en el medio del evento
I finished playing I sit down and next to me
yo termino de jugar me siento y al lado
sits the million well I'll look at that
se sienta el millón pues eso lo miro
today let's go they told me that you have a bad
hoy vamos me dijeron que tienes mal
feeling with me
rollo conmigo
I was waiting for the
yo estaba esperando que termine el
event to end to go talk to you says  no
evento para para ir a hablar te dice no
because I have the best with the
porque yo tengo la mejor con los
Argentinians that the two most beautiful months
argentinos que los dos meses más lindos
of my life I spent in Argentina and that
de mi vida los pasé en argentina y que
my girlfriend is Argentinian it doesn't matter they
mi novia es argentina no importa
are things that should be of interest like that
son cosas que tienen porqué interesar
but I swear problems of the
así pero se lo juro problemas del
interest of the Argentinians is like me
interés de los argentinos es como que yo
coming here Spain and they are treating me
venga acá españa que me están tratando
like a [ __ ] and saying -
de madre y diga
Juan Guarnizo messed with Coco the
-juan guarnizo se metió con coco los
Spaniards are all thieves they are all
españoles son todos chorros son todos
thieves but obviously he is going to interest me
ladrones pero obviamente que me va a
all of Spain and then say no here
inter toda españa y después decir no acá
pass the logo best months of my life
pase el logo mejores meses de mi vida
the Spaniards are going to say damn I don't
los españoles van a decir me
care that no no no no no no don't put it's
importa que no no no no no no no pongan
a joke look at a product it's a
es una broma mira un producto es una
joke very permanent with the joke he
broma bien permanente con la broma
was denying people who are
estaba negando a gente que le está
telling him my dad it was a joke well it
diciendo me papa era una broma bueno
turns out that the joke came true
resulta que la broma se hizo realidad
this morning well then I grabbed him and
esta mañana bueno entonces yo agarré y
said wood you can't mess with an
le dije wood no te puedes meter con un
entire country and a country that I am from I
país entero y un país del cual soy yo o
mean I am Argentinian and obviously I am
sea yo soy argentino y obviamente que
going to defend my country and I am going to
voy a defender a mi país y voy a
defend mine I mean nobody messes
defender a los míos o sea nadie se mete
with Argentina it's an equation of
con argentina es una ecuación de
belonging and no  but it seems
pertenencia y no pero a vos te parece
strong to you, they go with a lot of people to me
fuerte a mí me van con montón de gente
but you earned it efe anyway nothing
pero te lo ganaste efe igual nada
after there are other things that I'm not going to
después hay otras cosas que no las voy a
say because I'm not going to then I'm
decir porque tampoco lo voy a luego lo
going to sell it to the guy because
voy a vender al chabón porque
honestly I'm not a
sinceramente yo no soy un cabeza de
headstrong man I wasn't going to hit him just to hit him he
tacho yo no le iba a pegar por pegarle
came to talk to me I talked about the
me vino a hablar yo hablé de la
possibility of him talking I told him I
posibilidad de que hable le dije para mí
was totally wrong there's one who
estaba totalmente equivocado hay uno que
put something that I didn't like
puso algo que no me gustó
and I'm going to tell you I'll swallow it and I'm going to
y te voy a decir lo trago y les voy a
tell them something else here not for here the
decir otra cosa acá no para acá del
fact of hitting someone doesn't make you more
hecho de pegarle alguien no te hace más
handsome if there's a lack of respect that shouldn't be
guapo si hay falta de respeto que no hay
tolerated and I wasn't going to
que tolerar y que yo no las iba a
tolerate that rule about hitting then I think it
tolerar esa regla con pegar entonces
was very clear to him that you shouldn't get involved with the
creo que le quedó bien claro que con los
Argentinians it
argentinos no se tiene que meter terminó
all ended well yes it all ended well with him
todo bien si terminó todo bien yo a él
hui michu he already had it in for witch
ya hui michu se la tenía jurada a witch
a number I could still cross like I
un número pude cruzar todavía como he
said it's more personal and I think that
dicho ya es más personal y yo creo que
he did love me and there I would have to see
él sí me quería y ahí tendría que ver
what's going on but the best I'm not
qué es lo que pasa pero el mejor no me
going to they had said they don't go with you like the
voy a no habían dicho no te van como el
son he's going to panic you're not going to  nothing
son te va a tener pánico no te va nada
came to talk to me wave full avoiding
vino a hablarme onda full evitar el
conflict which the banks the bank
conflicto lo cual los bancos el banco la
non-violence I bank dialogue but
no violencia' banco el diálogo pero
also I bank that people are
también banco que la gente sea
respectful and
respetuosa y
and the reality friends is that beyond the fact
y la realidad amigos es que más allá de
that 95% of the chat agrees with
que el 95% del chat está de acuerdo con
what I'm saying if there is 5% they
lo que estoy diciendo si hay un 5% me
can suck my dick well because
puede chupar bien la porque
evidently they don't have a [ __ ] sense
evidentemente no tienen un sentido
of belonging nobody is going to interfere or in
de pertenencia nadie se va a meter o en
Argentina nobody is going to speak badly of my
argentina nadie va a hablar mal de mi
country less in front of me and if I tell you
país menos adelante mío y si yo te digo
that I oea at some point we are going
que te la oea en algún momento nos vamos
to enter we are going to meet and in that at
a entrar nos vamos encontrar y en eso en
that moment we have to see what it is that we
ese momento tenemos que ver qué es lo
do me in the traveling reality of
que hacemos yo en la realidad viajera de
another imbecile who thinks that this happened in
otro imbécil que se piensa que eso ha
1997 but you have balls of this
1997 pero tenéis los huevos de este
size friend who does that has happened
tamaño amigo que hace eso se ha dado
look bathed idiot I think that sometimes you
mira bañado yo creo que a veces
have to set an example it would have been
hay que dar el ejemplo hubiera sido más
easier to hit him if it had been easier to
fácil pegarle si hubiera sido más fácil
hit him but he is going to remain as an
pegarle pero se va a quedar como un
underachiever and he is going to speak badly of the
infradotado y va a hablar mal de los
Argentines and I would hit him at the event
argentinos y yo le pegaba en el evento
that is true exactly that is the
eso sí es verdad exactamente
question I am
eso esa es la cuestión
sure you can  hit someone you
seguro que le puedes pegar a alguien
probably haven't seen the body that
seguramente no se ha visto el cuerpo que
the kid has but he'll probably grab him
tiene el chaval pero seguramente lo coge
and break him but you can't you can't
y lo revienta pero no puedes no puedes
hit people and I wasn't about to
pegarle a la gente y tampoco estaba por
hit him because the guy came to
no pegarle porque el tipo vino a
talk to me and he admitted his mistake and
hablarme y reconoció el error y
showed that he told me that to the
demostró que me dijo que a los
Argentinians the reality is that
argentinos la realidad es que de todas
anyway for me he would have to
maneras para mí tendría que pedirle
apologize to all the Argentinians that the
disculpas a todos los argentinos que el
offense when he said what he said
agravio cuando dijo lo que dijo de todas
anyway everything is fine with the sun I don't
maneras está todo bien con el sol yo no
have any problem with the staff
tengo ningún problema con el personal
but he did clarify that for me my country is
pero sí aclaró que para mí mi país es
sacred or Argentina for me it is
sagrado o sea argentina para mí es
sacred oh I shot myself from useful pockets
sagrado uy me chuté desde útil bolsillos
in the head friends that
en la cabeza amigos
's what I tell you there's no need to look for
es lo que yo les digo no hay que buscar
people who are crazy people who are what they should be
a la gente que está loca a la gente que
left alone and
está lo que hay que dejarla tranquila y
I'm crazy so it's better that you
yo estoy loco entonces mejor que me
leave me alone they have to
dejen tranquilo a mí me lo tienen que
hit me with bottles and they have to kill me if you
pegar botellas y me tiene que matar si
don't kill me hide where you can
no me matas escóndete donde puedes
hide because I don't stop it's something that I have had
esconderte porque yo no paro es algo que
since my whole life and if friends
tengo desde toda mi vida y que si amigos
want to take me off well it's better that you kill me
me quiere despegar bueno mejor que me
because then I go and go and go and
mates porque después voy y voy y voy y
go until  I win I never lose in
voy hasta que gano yo nunca pierdo en
those things
esas cosas
but it's like he never loses his
pero es que como que nunca pierde el
cool I mean really uncle
frío o sea que de verdad tío
Cristian thanks a lot king
cristian muchas gracias rey
man you're really not right you
tío de verdad no tienes razón
lose when you hit someone like you
se pierde cuando le pegas a alguien como
never lose I
que nunca pierdes
mean I go I go until
o sea voy voy hasta
then I don't know of course if someone comes he
entonces no me sé claro si alguien viene
hits me with a bottle well I can
me pega un botellazo pues yo le puedo
respond with a katana and if someone
responder con una catana y si alguien
comes then of course let's see who hits
viene entonces claro a ver quién se pega
harder let's
más
see if they kill each other with a single but
a ver si se mata ante un sencillo pero
seriously
en serio
man seriously no
hombre en serio no
no god you
no dios no
're not okay in case they try to
estáis bien en caso de que le intenten
hit you Javi of course they
pegar javi de claro por supuesto se
try to hit you direct defend but
intentan pegarte dirige defender pero
because they make a criticism on the internet
porque te hagan una crítica en internet
or had a joke go to some
o tenían un chiste que vaya a algún
joke in your country a joke about Maradona
chiste a tu país un chiste a maradona
man please
hombre por favor
go no I don't have a problem I'm not
recorre no no tengo problema no tengo
afraid no no it's a matter of my blood
miedo no no es una cuestión de que me de
not my blood I would only
la sangre no me de la sangre nada más
defend continue as an Argentine
defendería seguir como un argentino
totally I was doing well my friend I mean that's what I
totalmente iba bien mi amigo o sea en
said to my people
eso es lo que dijo yo a mi gente la
death I mean to my people to the death I mean
muerte o sea a mi gente a muerte o sea
come whoever comes say what they say I'm
venga el que venga digan lo que digan yo
going to the death my friends my family are
voy a muerte mis amigos mi familia son
untouchable that's true a long time ago  that I
intocables eso sí hace tiempo que me
wanted this type of performances
quería que este tipo de actuaciones
goddesses of defending people and your
diosas de defender a la gente y tus
arguments in this way is already far
argumentos de esta forma ya quedó muy
behind man I believed that and my country
atrás tío yo me creía eso y mi país
too so let them know and these
también entonces que lo sepan y estas
things there are
cosas
people who do not fully understand it
hay gente que no termina de comprender
is fine that the creators should not
está bien que los creadores no deban
educate anyone but they have a
educar a nadie pero tienen un trabajo
public job just like a policeman or a
público igual que un policía o una
cashier and education and behavior is expected that was what I
cajera y se espera educación y
said at the beginning he proved to be a
fue lo que dije al inicio demostró ser
bad person and he is one of the Argentines
mala de persona y es de los argentinos
who are ashamed and made him famous in the
que dan pena y lo hicieron famoso en la
same sentence he says that violence is
misma frase dice que la violencia está
wrong and then threatens with blows
mal y luego amenaza con golpes
found more than once he threatened him among the
hallado más de una vez lo amenazó entre
same colleagues also the can is
los mismos colegas también el lata está
very normalized and the way he has
muy normalizado y la forma que tiene
precisely because of those attitudes
precisamente por esas actitudes
flip out no
flipa no
umayya the same already the same that he
omeya lo mismo ya lo mismo que
did it more times like super 8 it
lo hizo más veces como el super 8
is not the true attitude it
no es la actitud de verdad
going to see what the best says
voy a ver qué dice el mejor
today
al día
give me my welcome ball how he took away the
dame mi welcome ball como le quitó los
weening
weening
how he defended you he's going to select video
como te defendió va a seleccionar vídeo
movements me with a pizza because he
movimientos me con una pizza porque
took that photo of mine this affects you I
cogía esa foto mía este te afecta me lo
saw it we already tried let's react enjoy
vi ya probamos reaccionemos disfruta de
your day he loves you
tu día el te quiero
oh  lic about your girlfriend
ay lic sobre tu novia
women
mujeres
by the way it was me since they hadn't said
por cierto fui yo como no habían
hello or anything I guess because there was
saludado ni nada supongo porque había
bad vibes you know on his part not on mine
mal rollo sabes por su parte por la mía
but I went to talk to him I sat
no pero yo fui a hablar con él me senté
next to him and I'm going to talk to no one
a su lado y voy a hablar con nadie
else I didn't even know we
nada más yo no sabía ni siquiera que
were there I went to say hello when I
estábamos ahí yo le fui a saludar cuando
saw him they announced how he was going to participate
lo vi anunciaron de cómo va a participar
and like who set up to participate drum
y como cual montó a participar bombo el
coss's friend whose I thought wow of
amigo de coss cuyo pensé guau desde
course they returned me death I'm going to say
luego me devolvieron muerte yo voy a
hello let's see what happened it's simply
saludar a ver qué pasó simplemente es
with maradona argentina his death I
con maradona argentina suyo muerte ya no
can't understand that's why people are so
puedo entender por eso la gente como tan
fanatical about something but in all senses
fanática de algo pero en todos sentidos
me because of the way I am I can't be a
yo por mi forma de ser no puedo ser
fanatic to such an extreme of anything no matter how
fanático hasta tal extremo de nada por
much I like something a lot no matter how much I
mucho que algo me guste mucho por mucho
support something it never ends up mattering that much to me you
que apoye algo nunca llega a importarme
know but although I know something very
tanto sabes pero aunque sé algo muy
close I don't know he commented that it's my family you
cercano no sé comentó que es mi familia
know roig or a very close friend of mine
sabes lo roig o algún amigo mío muy
or something like that it's not going to matter that
cercano o algo así no va a importar a
much although I am interested in a game
dar tanto aunque me interés una partida
of the chinese or other things but it's not
de los chinos ni más cosas pero que no
bad I simply don't understand it doesn't have to be
es malo simplemente yo no entiendo no
bad to be a fan of
tiene por qué ser malo ser fanático de
something I
algo
don't know how it would have  reacted if it had
no sé cómo habría reaccionado si os
happened to you I'm not an
hubiera pasado no soy una persona
aggressive person but I am proud you know I don't
agresiva pero si soy orgulloso sabes no
[ __ ] myself you'll see in the
se caga vas a ver en la situación
hypothetical situation I would have [ __ ] myself maybe
hipotética me habría cagado quizás hace
a year and a half ago currently I have the
un año y medio actualmente tengo los
balls this big in plan to
así de gordos en plan para
hit me now after what happened in
pegarme ahora bien después de lo del
boxing after he hit me up
boxeo después de que me haya pegado
to the prompter I'm not
hostias hasta el apuntador no tengo
afraid to hit not even the pp but 0000 and I don't care that's
miedo de pegar ni el pp pero 0000 y me
real I mean
da igual eso es real es decir que ahora
right now there will find a situation where
mismo encontrará una situación donde
someone wants to hit me obviously if I'm
alguien me quiere pegar obviamente si yo
afraid that he has a knife or
tengo miedo a que tenga una navaja o
something like that then I am the most
algo estilo ahí sí que soy por lo más
coherent but if it's someone like that
coherente pero si es alguien en plan que
wants to hit me with their fists right
me quiere pegar con los puños yo ahora
now I wouldn't love it with me he knows how to
mismo no me encantaría conmigo sabe
hit or the other way around
pegar o al revés
meccano because a referee came son
mecano porque vino un árbitro hijo
rebeta won but if it had been a
rebeta ganado pero si llega a ser una
fight to the death with river he would put us in the
pelea muerte con river nos subirá al
ring and without a plan the last one alive would come out to
ring y sin plan sale el último con vida
win an event
ganar un evento compite
Shakira and her children would have died
shakira y sus hijos habrían muerto
against as it depends on the experience
contra como depende de la experiencia
he has
que tenga él
in making me Ruben won but the one who had
en hacerme ganó rubén pero el que estuvo
pain in his ribs for the
con dolor de costillas durante las
next two weeks was really revenge I
próximas dos semanas fue re vengo yo
yes
sí
black in  tuna rhesus screamed for 5
black en atún sea rhesus grito por 5
months wv
meses wv
messed with all the Argentinians he treated
se metió con todos los argentinos trato
everyone like ignorant people and then he was a
a todos de ignorantes y después fue un
pretty xenophobic guy and talking about what
chico bastante xenófobo y hablar de lo
had happened with the only thing to see that
que había pasado con lo único haber eso
is very relative there we disagreed a little
es muy relativo allí discrepamos un poco
in our conversation okay that was
en nuestra conversación vale eso fue
where we did not agree when we
donde no estuvimos de acuerdo cuando
spoke because he told me is that you
hablamos porque él me dijo es que
uploaded that and it means that he is xenophobic xenophobic
subiste eso y quiere decir que es
we are going to go in
xenófobo xenófobo nos vamos a ir en
Spanish and that you hate Argentinians
castellano y que odias a los argentinos
and such but there I disagreed a little me
y tal pero ahí discrepaba un poco yo
why are you guys let's see if I upload
porque se andan vamos a ver que yo suba
a meme I do not do it because I think what is
un meme no lo hago porque opino lo que
told to me the other way around a meme is
se me dice al revés un meme es
literally to make a joke to make
literalmente para hacer broma para hacer
humor then it is a joke you make humor it is
humor entonces es broma haces humor es
because it is literally saying something
porque literalmente está diciendo algo
that you do not think and you take everything to the
que no piensas y lo llegas todo al
exaggerated extreme you know with which why
extremo exagerado sabes con lo cual que
I put it to touch the support I was not
por qué lo puse a tocar la apoya no fui
wrong ballet I show to the late well that
mal encaminado ballet muestro al tarde
the grace the humor the grace the
pues que la gracia el humor la gracia el
humor is to bother someone if you do not
humor es molestar a alguien si no
bother someone only tomorrow is
molestas a alguien solamente tomorrow es
very funny it is always that you know the
muy divertido es siempre eso sabes el
humor says  check it out on his channel where he
humor dice checa mejor en su canal donde
reacts to the videos the best
reacciona los vídeos el mejor
game is to
game es
finish the trip
acabar el viaje
to Kuma just sucked my whole ear
a kuma me acaba de chupar toda la oreja
day
día
[Laughs]
[Risas]
and
e
here
aquí
and it's
y
not possible but let's see what he said
no se puede pero vamos a ver lo que dijo
that's not the topic
ese no es el tema
we expected
esperábamos
then how is it
entonces como es
like the dynasty
como la dinastía
with the participation of Marquito Navajas
con la participación de marquito navajas
and Enrico as a normal person it doesn't
y enrico como una persona normal no me
paint me like if what I was telling you today
pinta la de si lo que te decía hoy
we had weddings if it doesn't go but let's go
tuvimos casamientos si no va pero vamos
what he said that I said
que lo que ha dicho que lo he dicho
say Mercedes we
decir mercedes
decided that the writing don't tell me what he
decidimos que el escrito no me diga qué
said
es lo que ha dicho
tell me that I imagine
decidme que imagino
videos past broadcasts that no one
vídeos emisiones pasadas que nadie no se
sees doesn't come out I don't know why
ve no sale no sé por qué
but well can't you tell me what he
pero bueno no me podéis decir que lo que
said
ha dicho
thank you very much
gracias muchísimas gracias
we saved it
la guardamos
nothing is everything fine tomorrow he goes to the
nada está todo bien mañana va hasta el
mountain and I'm going to propose to Clestin
monte y yo le va a proponer a célestin
together
juntos
uncle
tío
those things gave us
esas cosas nos dio
[Music]
[Música]